firestonecompleteautocare.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Firestone Complete Auto Care

Firestone Complete Auto Care thanks you for accessing or using this web site (the “Site”). Firestone Complete Auto Care wants to assure you that Firestone Complete Auto Care respects your privacy. Firestone Complete Auto Care knows that trust is the key to any successful business relationship. The following Privacy Policy describes Firestone Complete Auto Care’s commitment to protect your personal information.

Use of this Site constitutes your consent to the collection and use of the information as described below in this Privacy Policy. If Firestone Complete Auto Care changes this Privacy Policy, Firestone Complete Auto Care will update this page of the Site so that you will be aware of any changes to this policy. Firestone Complete Auto Care encourages you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated.

This Privacy Policy explains how Firestone Complete Auto Care collects, uses and discloses your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps Firestone Complete Auto Care has taken to ensure that your personal information is secure. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your choices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.

**THE SITE INCLUDES LINKS TO THE WEB SITES OF THIRD PARTIES. WE PROVIDE THESE LINKS AS A CONVENIENCE TO OUR USERS. THE INCLUSION OF ANY LINK DOES NOT IMPLY FIRESTONE COMPLETE AUTO CARE’S ENDORSEMENT OF ANY COMPANY, ITS WEB SITE, OR THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IT SELLS. PLEASE NOTE THAT FIRESTONE COMPLETE AUTO CARE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF ANY WEB SITE OTHER THAN OUR OWN SITE.**

**THE SITE ALSO INCLUDES CERTAIN PAGES THAT ARE “FRAMED” TO PROVIDE INFORMATION FROM WEB SITES OF THIRD PARTIES. SUCH FRAMED PAGES WILL BE IDENTIFIED ON THE PAGE AND THE PAGE OWNER IDENTIFIED. WE PROVIDE THESE FRAMED PAGES AS A CONVENIENCE TO OUR USERS. PLEASE NOTE THAT FIRESTONE COMPLETE AUTO CARE IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONTENT OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF ANY FRAMED PAGES. THE TERMS AND POLICIES OF THE PAGE OWNER IDENTIFIED ON THE FRAMED PAGE WILL CONTROL.**

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

**INFORMATION COLLECTION.**  
Firestone Complete Auto Care may collect information from you at several different points and in different ways on this Site Firestone Complete Auto Care will ask you for your permission before Firestone Complete Auto Care collects any information that personally identifies you or allows Firestone Complete Auto Care to contact you. Firestone Complete Auto Care’s primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with an efficient, meaningful and customized experience. For example, Firestone Complete Auto Care can use your personal information to:  

  * make this Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * help you quickly find information and services.
  * help Firestone Complete Auto Care create content on this Site that is most relevant to you.
  * alert you to updated information and services offered by Firestone Complete Auto Care, or its affiliated companies.

**(a) Registration.**  To use this Site, or certain portions or features of the Site, you may be required to first complete an online registration form. During registration you will be prompted to provide to Firestone Complete Auto Care certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, address, phone number and email address.  

**(b) Cookies.**  “Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by a user’s Internet browser on a user’s hard drive. The Site may store some information on your computer in the form of a cookie or similar file, however This Site does not use permanent cookies that contain any personally identifying information, such as your name or address. The cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to our site and may also be matched and combined with personally identifiable information collected from other sources to provide you with a customized experience that we feel will be of value to you. Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you do elect to disable the Site’s cookies, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of the Site.  

In addition, this site uses the following Google Analytics Advertising Features:

  * Remarketing with Google Analytics
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
  * Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data for advertising purposes, including the collection of data via advertising cookies and identifiers

We share the data collected using Google Analytics with a trusted set of third-party vendors and use it to help us analyze how users use our Site. Google Analytics plants a cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this Site. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this Site is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this Site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser, or following the [Google opt-out process](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**(c) Log Files.**  This Site automatically collects information pertaining to Your access. Such information may include Your Internet protocol (“IP”) address as well as other connection and usage information for system administration and troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address indicates the location of Your computer on the Internet.) Firestone Complete Auto Care does not link an IP address to any personally identifiable information.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).**  
This Site is a website directed to the general public. Firestone Complete Auto Care does not knowingly collect information from children under 13.

**INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE.**  
**(a) Internal Use.** Firestone Complete Auto Care may identify you in connection with your use of certain aspects of this Site. For example, Firestone Complete Auto Care may identify you by vehicle or tire ownership to provide you with information on related products and/or promotions. Firestone Complete Auto Care may internally use your personal information to improve Firestone Complete Auto Care’s marketing and promotional efforts, to improve the Site’s content and/or layout, and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.

**(b) External Use.** Firestone Complete Auto Care does not sell, rent, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information to any third parties, excluding affiliated companies, without your consent. Occasionally, Firestone Complete Auto Care may provide statistics to outside parties about the usage of our site, but these statistics will never include any personal information about our users. Firestone Complete Auto Care may disclose your personal information pursuant to a court or government order. Firestone Complete Auto Care will share your information with affiliated companies to identify services or products that you may be of interest to you (Marketing) but you will have the opportunity to opt-out of this Marketing.

Please note that because a customer information database is customarily considered a business asset, Firestone Complete Auto Care reserves the right to transfer the database in a merger or sale of some or all of its company or in an action for bankruptcy. Your information will continue to be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy by the acquiring or merged company unless you are notified and provided an opportunity to change your preferences.

**DATA SECURITY  
**This Site incorporates various physical, electronic and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, the servers where Firestone Complete Auto Care stores your personal information are kept in a secure environment, behind locked doors and a firewall.

WHILE FIRESTONE COMPLETE AUTO CARE HAS TAKEN COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE PRECAUTIONS TO SAFEGUARD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, FIRESTONE COMPLETE AUTO CARE CANNOT GUARANTEE COMPLETE SECURITY BECAUSE COMPLETE SECURITY DOES NOT PRESENTLY EXIST ON THE INTERNET.

**OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS  
**Upon your request, Firestone Complete Auto Care will (a) remove your personal information from Firestone Complete Auto Care’s database (which might cancel your subscription to this Site or a portion of this Site); or (b) correct or update your personal information. You can request that Firestone Complete Auto Care remove, correct or update your personal information at the “Contact Us” section of this Site.

**UPDATES TO THIS POLICY  
**If Firestone Complete Auto Care decides to change or update this Privacy Policy, Firestone Complete Auto Care will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information Firestone Complete Auto Care collects, uses and distributes. Firestone Complete Auto Care encourages you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about Firestone Complete Auto Care’s Privacy Policy, please use the “Contact Us” section of this Site.

* References to Firestone Complete Auto Care in this privacy policy includes Tires Plus, Hibdon Tires Plus, Wheel Works and other trade names under which Bridgestone Retail Operations operates.

**© 2018 Firestone Complete Auto Care. All rights reserved.**
